[音乐]
in this section we're going to overview
在本节中，我们将概述网络
the network core we're going to see what happens inside the network core and
core 我们将看看网络核心内部发生了什么
我们将介绍一些重要的话题
we're going to introduce a number of
and we're going to introduce a number of
我们将介绍一些重要的话题
important topics we'll talk about backward forwarding packet queuing delays and packet loss we'll
我们将讨论后向转发数据包排队延迟和数据包丢失
我们将讨论称为电路的分组交换的替代方案
important topics we'll talk about backward forwarding packet queuing delays and packet loss we'll
talk about an alternative to packet switching known as circuit switching and we'll talk
切换，我们将讨论的结构
互联网我们会明白我们所说的意思
about the structure of the internet we'll see what we mean when we say
互联网是一个网络网络，网络核心仅由一个
the internet is a network of networks
the network core consists simply of a
通过一组互连的一组路由器
set of routers that are interconnected
by a set
通信链路和互联网的核心运营基于
of communication links and the
internet's core operation is based on a
被称为分组交换的原理其实比较简单
principle known as packet switching
which is really relatively simple the
想法是以下发生的事情是最终主持
idea is the following
what happens is that the end hosts that
我们前面讲过把应用程序级别的消息划分
we talked about earlier
take application level messages divide
将这些消息放入数据块中将这些数据块放入数据包中
those messages into chunks of data
put those chunks of data inside packets
并将这些数据包发送到互联网现在这些数据包
and send those packets
into the internet now those packets are
然后沿着来自源的路径转发
then
forwarded along a path from a source
节点到目标节点，例如从
node
to a destination node for example from a
网络服务器可能连接到运行网络浏览器的笔记本电脑
web server maybe to your laptop
that's running running a web browser
从那个网络服务器发出一个请求，所以让我们解压
that made a request
from that web server so let's unpack
最后的声明只是一点点，因为我们实际上听到了很多
that last statement just a little bit
because we actually heard a lot of
重要的话我们谈到了转发
important words there we talked about
forwarding
我们讨论了从源到目的地的路径 我们讨论了一个源
we talked about a path from source to
destination and we talked about a source
和目的地有两个关键功能执行
and a destination
there are two key functions performed
在网络核心转发有时也称为
inside the network core
forwarding sometimes also known as
交换和路由 让我们来看看路由器内部
switching and routing
let's take a look inside a router so we
可以看到这些函数转发的是一个本地操作它是关于
can see what these functions are
forwarding is a local action it's about
从路由器的输入链路移动到达的数据包
moving an arriving packet from the
router's input link
到适当的路由器输出链路转发由转发控制
to the appropriate router output link
forwarding is controlled by a forwarding
我们在这里看到的表，里面有一个转发表
table that we see here
and there's a forwarding table inside
互联网上数以百万计的路由器中的每一个
each and every of the millions of
routers in the internet
当数据包到达时，路由器会在数据包内部查找目的地 址，然后查找目标地址
when a packet arrives a router will look
inside the packet for a destination
当数据包到达时，路由器会在数据包内部查找目的地 址，然后查找目标地址
address
and then look up the destination address
在我们在这里看到的转发表中，然后传输传入的数据包
in its forwarding table as we see here
and then transmit that incoming packet
在通向该目的地的输出链接上
on the output link
that leads to that destination well
在概念上查找和转发非常简单，但您可能会
that's pretty simple conceptually
look up and forwarding but you might be
想知道里面的内容怎么样
wondering
well how are the contents of that
首先创建的转发表就是
forwarding table
created in the first place and that's
我们遇到第二个关键函数的地方
where we encounter the second key
function
网络核心的路由路由是全局动作
of the network core and that's routing  is the global action of
routing is the global action of
确定数据包采用的源到目标路径，我们将看到
determining the source to destination paths taken by packets as we'll see routing algorithms
路由算法计算这些路径并计算每个路由器的本地
compute these paths and compute the local per router forwarding tables needed to realize
实现这种端到端所需的转发表
转发路径 一个很好的类比，可以理解
compute these paths and compute the local per router forwarding tables needed to realize
this end-to-end forwarding path a good analogy for understanding the difference between forwarding and
转发和路由的区别是考虑
我最近从圣何塞开车去旅行
routing is to think about taking a trip in a car i recently drove
加州一路到东海岸
from san jose california all the way to the east coast to northampton massachusetts
北安普敦马萨诸塞州这是一次长途旅行
好吧，我决定在这里走这条上层路线
it was a long trip well i decided to take this upper route here
而不是这里的这条较低的路线，那就是路线决定
rather than this lower route here and
that's the routing decision
这就是从源头获取的路径
that's made the path that's taken from
the source
加利福尼亚州圣何塞到目的地北安普敦马萨诸塞州
san jose california to the destination
northampton massachusetts
现在当我到达一个交汇处时说在加利福尼亚州萨克拉门托
now when i get to an interchange say in
sacramento california
我正在进入城市的输入道路之一
i'm coming into the city on one of the
input roads
我需要被转送出城
and i need to be forwarded out of the
city on an
克利夫兰的输出道路在这里以及沿途的所有交叉路口
output road in cleveland here and really
at all intersections along the way
从输入道路切换到输出道路是局部的
that switching from an input road to an
output road is the local
具有全局路由功能确定的转发功能
forwarding function with the global
routing function determining
我实际转发到哪条输出道路上
which of the output roads i'm actually
forwarded onto
您可能想稍微考虑一下本地之间的这种关系
you might want to think just a bit about
this relationship between the local
转发功能和全局路由功能可以
forwarding function
and the global routing function can you
想想其他的类比让我们接下来关注传输
think of other analogies
let's next focus on the transmission of
网络核心路由器上的数据包位
packet bits at a router in the network
core
在这个图中，我们在这里说明了正在传输的数据包中的位
in this figure here we're illustrating
the bits in a packet being transmitted
从一个路由器到下一个你希望你还记得我们说过
from one router to the next
you'll hopefully recall that we said
如果一个数据包的 l 位长并且链路传输
that if a packet's
l bits long and the link transmission
速率是每秒 r 位，然后将用 l 除以 r
rate is r bits per second
then it's going to take l divided by r
将数据包传输到链路传输位的秒数将是
seconds to transmit the packet
into the link transmitted bits will be
在接收端接收并收集
received
and gathered up at the receiving end of
一个链接，直到收到完整的数据包
a link
until the full packet has been received
你可以看到这里收集的比特和数据包
you can see the bits and the packets
being gathered up here
一旦数据包被完全接收，它就可以被转发到下一跳
once the packet's been fully received it
can then be forwarded on to the next hop
等等，这就是所谓的数据包的存储和转发操作
and so on this is what's known as the
store and forward operation of a packet
现在切换网络让我们仔细看看什么
switch network
now let's take a closer look at what
当数据包到达路由器进行转发时发生
happens as packet arrived to a router
for forwarding
在这张图中，我们看到了一个带有三个链接的路由器
in this figure here we see a router with
three links
让我们假设主机 a 正在向主机 c 发送数据包
let's assume that host a is sending
packets to host c
并且主机 b 正在向主机 e 发送数据包，现在让我们仔细看看
and host b is sending packets to host e
and now let's take a close look at the
输入链路速率 链路的传输速率 r 从
input link rates
the transmission rate r of the link from
a 到第一跳路由器是每秒 100 兆比特
a to the first hop router is 100
megabits per second
从 b 到第一跳路由器的第二条链路也是如此
as is the second link from b to the
first hop router
但是从第一跳路由器到第二跳路由器的链路的传输速率
but the transmission rate of the link
from the first hop router to the second
跳路由器每秒只有 1.5 兆比特
hop router is only 1.5 megabits per
second
它几乎慢了 100 倍，这与家庭中的情况相差不远
it's almost 100 times slower and this
isn't far from the case in a home
家庭网络路由器可能在家中连接了以太网的网络
network where the home network router
may have attached ethernets in the home
以每秒千兆位或每秒 54 兆位的 wi-fi 运行
running at a gigabit per second or wi-fi
at 54 megabits per second
但是到电缆标题的访问链接要慢得多，也许只是
but the access link to the cable heading
is much slower perhaps only
每秒 5 或 10 兆位，所以问题来了
5 or 10 megabits per second and so
here's the question
当数据包到达这个第一跳路由器时会发生什么
what happens as packets arrive to this
first hop router
这个例子中的路由器只能以每秒 1.5 兆比特的速度传输
well the router in this example can only
transmit at 1.5 megabits per second
当然，数据包的到达速度可以比每秒 1.5 兆比特快得多
and certainly packets can arrive a lot
faster than 1.5 megabits per second
如果 a 和 b 同时传输大量数据包
if a and b are both transmitting a lot
of packets at the same time
如果太多的数据包以太快的速度到达，则会形成一个数据包队列
if too many packets arrive at too fast a
rate then a queue of packets will form
在如图所示的第一跳路由器中发生排队
in that first hop router
as shown in the figure queuing happens
每当工作比某些服务设施更快到达时
whenever work arrives
faster than some service facility can
实际上为这项工作提供服务，当然我们都熟悉这里的队列
actually serve that work and of course
we're all familiar with queues here's a
等待在收费站获得服务的汽车队列
queue of cars waiting to get service at
a toll booth
我们在结账柜台排队等候
we wait in lines and stores at the
checkout counter
我想你们中的许多人一直在财务长办公室排队等候
and i imagine many of you have been
waiting at lines in the bursar's office
为了支付你的账单，这里有一群人在排队等候
to pay your bills
here's a group of people queuing to get
在一栋楼里，一群英国人在等着
in a building and here's a group of
folks in the uk waiting
如果你去过英国，你可能知道排队就是这个词
if you've been in the uk you probably
know that queuing is actually the word
英国人在排队时常说
that brits use to say when you're
waiting in line
英国人真的很擅长暗示看看这个视频
the brits are really good at cueing
check out this video
这是非常彻底的存在指南
this is the awfully thorough guide to
being
英国总督在这一集中叫 blimey 排队
british governor call blimey
in this episode queuing
[鼓掌] 如果排队是奥运项目
[Applause]
if queuing were an olympic event then
英国会赢得金牌然后等待一个小时
great britain would win
gold then it would wait for an hour take
一张票赢银牌和铜牌 没人排队
a ticket
and win silver and bronze no one queues
比英国人好，如果你想适应你需要
better than the british
and if you want to fit in you need to
知道规则
know the rules
好回到网络数据包线索将在路由器上形成
well to get back to networking packet
cues are going to form at a router's outbound link whenever the arrival rate
每当到达速率（以比特为单位）
输入链路上的秒超过传输速率比特每
in bits per second on the input link exceeds the transmission rate bits per
一段时间内的第二个输出链接
second of that output link for some period of time when there are packet
当有数据包队列时，他们将排队延迟
queues they're going to be queuing delays packets are going to have to wait
数据包将不得不在路由器中等待而不是被转发
in routers rather than being forwarded on their way to their destination and because
他们到达目的地的方式，因为只有这么多的记忆
将提示数据包存储在路由器中，队列变得太长并且
there's only so much memory to store cued packets in a router the queue
路由器的内存耗尽，到达的数据包可能会到达
becomes too long and a router's memory is exhausted an arriving packet may arrive
路由器并找不到可存储在其中的内存
to a router and find no memory in which to be stored in such
数据包将在该路由器上丢失或丢失的情况
cases a packet's going to be dropped or lost at that router and as
正如我们将看到的事实，数据包可能会延迟
we'll see the fact that packets can be delayed and or lost is going
和或丢失将成为头痛的主要来源
to be a major source of headaches for a lot of network protocols well
到目前为止，我们一直在谈论许多网络协议
包交换，我们刚刚看到包排队延迟
so far we've been talking about packet switching and we've just seen that packet
并且可能会发生丢包，因为网络并不总是控制
queuing delays and packet loss can happen because the network doesn't always control senders
发送者足够小心，以确保大的排队延迟和数据包丢失
carefully enough to ensure that large queuing delays and packet loss doesn't happen now
现在不会发生 包交换不是构建网络的唯一方法
packet switching is not the only way to build a network and indeed long
确实早在互联网出现之前，早在分组交换之前
before the internet was around and long before packet switching telephone networks employed a
电话网络采用了不同形式的技术
被称为电路交换让我们来看看电路交换
different form of technology known as circuit switching let's take a look at circuit
在电路交换中，有一个呼叫的概念而不是数据包的概念
switching in circuit switching there's a notion of a call rather than a notion
在呼叫开始之前从源流向目的地的所有
of packets that flow from source to destination before a call starts all of
该呼叫将需要的网络内资源
the resources within the network that are going to be needed for that call
分配给从源到目标的调用
are allocated to that call from source
to destination
所以一旦呼叫开始，呼叫将保留足够的传输
so once the call begins the call will
have reserved enough transmission
自身的能力，以确保排队将
capacity
for itself to ensure that queuing will
永远不会发生，除了
never
occur there's no delay other than
网络内传播延迟和数据不丢失
propagation delay and
no loss of data within the network
因为链路容量已被保留供此呼叫专用
because link capacity has been reserved
for the exclusive use of this call
在这个图中，这里的每个链接都有四个电路
in this diagram here each link has four
circuits
从左上角到右下角的呼叫被分配到第二个电路
the call from the top left to the bottom
right is allocated the second circuit
在顶部链接和右侧链接的第一个电路上
on the top link and the first circuit on
the right link
电路是不共享的专用资源
the circuits are dedicated resources
they're not shared
对于任何其他用户，它真的就像有一根电线
with any other users it's really like
there's a wire
从源头到目的地，所以这一切听起来都不错
from source to destination so all this
sounds pretty good
没有延迟没有损失没有比这更好的了
no delays no loss doesn't get any better
than that
直到你开始考虑这样一个事实，因为资源是为
until you start to think about the fact
that since resources are reserved for
呼叫的独占使用，但电路可以空闲，如果有
the exclusive use of a call
but the circuits can go idle if there's
没有数据可发送该呼叫，如果带宽不足，则存在问题
no data to send on that call
and there's the rub if the bandwidth
没有被呼叫使用它丢失了没有其他人没有其他呼叫可以
isn't used by the call
it's lost no one else no other calls can
使用它，因此电路交换网络可以
use it
and so a circuit switch network can be
正如我们将在第二个电路交换中看到的那样，效率低下是在两个电路中的一个中完成的
inefficient as we'll see in a second
circuit switching is done in one of two
频分复用 fdm 或
ways either
frequency division multiplexing fdm or
时分复用 tdm in fdm 电磁或光谱
time division multiplexing tdm in fdm
the electromagnetic or optical spectrum
被划分为窄频带，并且每个呼叫都被分配其中之一
is divided into narrow frequency bands
and each call is allocated one of those
窄带，可以全速率传输
narrow bands
and can transmit at the full rate
该频段在 tdm 时间内允许被划分为时隙和
allowed by that band
in tdm time is divided into slots and
每个调用都分配了一组周期性的时隙
each call is allocated a periodic set of
slots
源只能在其分配的时隙内传输，但可以这样做
a source can transmit only during its
allocated time slots but can do so
以该更宽频带的更高最大速率
at the higher maximum rate of that wider
frequency band
既然我们已经介绍了电路交换和
so now that we've been introduced to the
notion of both circuit switching and
分组交换让我们看一个数值例子
packet switching
let's take a look at a numerical example
查看在特定情况下可支持的用户数量
to look at the numbers of users
that are supportable in a specific
网络场景 这是我们要查看的场景
networking scenario
here's the scenario we want to look at
让我们假设我们有一个千兆每秒的链接
let's assume that we've got a gigabit
per second link
有最终用户，每个最终用户的行为如下
there are end users and each of these
end users behaves as follows
当他们有数据要发送时，他们需要发送
when they have data to send they need to
send at
每秒兆位，占整个链路带宽的十分之一
megabits per second that's one-tenth of
the overall link bandwidth
然而，用户只会有 10 次忙碌，这意味着 90% 的时间
however users are only going to be busy
10 of the time that means 90 percent of
他们没有数据要发送的时候让我们来看看 一个关于有多少分组交换用户和
the time
they have no data to send let's take a
他们没有数据要发送的时候让我们来看看 一个关于有多少分组交换用户和
look at a numerical example
about how many packet-switched users and
可以支持多少电路交换机用户
how many circuit switch users can be
supported
在这个网络设置中，让我们假设 n
in this network setting let's suppose
that n
对于电路切换的情况下是 35 个用户，计算很容易
is 35 users for the case of circuit
switching the calculation is easy
每个用户在电路交换下需要每秒 100 兆比特
each user needs 100 megabits per second
under circuit switching
所以一个电路交换网络最多可以支持
and so a circuit switch network can
support at most
一次 10 个用户 现在让我们来看看数据包交换
10 users at a time now let's take a look
at packet switching
请记住，每个用户每秒需要 100 兆比特，因此我们可以支持
remember each user needs a hundred
megabits per second so we can support
10个分组交换用户就像我们可以支持10个电路交换用户
10 packet switched users just like we
can support 10 circuit switch users
没问题，但请记住，每个用户只有 10 次忙，如果
no problem but remember each user is
only busy 10 of the time what happens if
我们允许所有 35 个用户进入系统
we allow
all 35 users into the system what's the
其中超过 10 个处于活动状态的概率
probability that more than 10 of these
are active
在给定时间有超过 10 个活跃用户
at a given time with more than 10 active
users
这是队列形成和增长的唯一时间
that's the only time queues are going to
form and grow
可以用一些不需要的基本概率和组合来表示
one can show with some basic probability
and combinatorics which are not required
对于这个类，所以我们不会在这里进行计算
for this class and so we won't go into
this calculation here
35 个用户中有 10 个以上处于活动状态的时间比例
that the fraction of time that more than
10 of the 35 users are active
零点 0 0 4 即如果我们让所有 35 个用户进入
is point zero 0 0
4 that is if we let all 35 users into
系统处于数据包交换状态，然后排队的时间百分比
the system under packet switching
then the percentage of time when queues
将开始增长小于百分之四
will start to grow
is less than four one hundredths of one
百分比的时间这是一个非常小的数字，也许我们是
percent of the time
that's a pretty small number maybe we're
愿意忍受一些非常偶然的延迟和损失
willing to put up with some
very occasional delay and loss in order
允许所有 35 个，而不仅仅是 10 个
to allow
all 35 rather than just 10
用户进入系统时，这种在数据包交换下的性能增益称为
users into the system this performance
gain under packet switching is known as
分组交换的统计复用增益，这是一个关键
the statistical multiplexing gain
of packet switching and it was a key
发明分组交换时使用分组交换的论据 60
argument for using packet switching
when packet switching was invented 60
多年前现在你觉得那个包
years ago
it may seem to you now that packet
自切片面包以来，切换几乎是最好的事情
switching is just about the best thing
since sliced bread
它是灌篮冠军吗？看起来是这样
is it a slam dunk winner it might seem
so
甚至今天的电话网络实际上也承载着数据
and even today's telephone networks
actually carry data
这些天在包里所以在某种意义上我们可以声明
in packets these days so in some sense
we could declare
数据包交换获胜者 数据包交换特别适用于
packet switching a winner package
switching is particularly great for
当源只是偶尔有数据时的突发数据
bursty data
when a source only occasionally has data
发送很简单，没有呼叫设置
to send
it's simple there's no call setup
没有资源预留主机只是开始发送它的数据
there's no resource reservation
a host just starts sending data that it
必须发送我们已经看到拥塞数据包延迟
has to send
we've seen that congestion packet delay
损失可能会发生，但我们也会看到互联网
and loss can happen
but we'll also see that internet
协议 tcp 尤其会对拥塞做出反应
protocols tcp
in particular will react to congestion
通过降低发送方的发送速率
by
decreasing the sender's sending rate in
面对拥塞所以拥塞和损失在某种意义上可以
the face of congestion
so congestion and loss can in some sense
避免或至少减轻是否有可能提供类似电路的
be avoided or at least mitigated
is it possible to provide circuit-like
包交换的行为以及俗话说它很复杂
behavior with packet switching
well as the saying goes it's complicated
但我们将研究各种尝试尽可能像电路一样的技术
but we'll study various techniques that
try to be as circuit-like as possible
好吧，让我们回到网络核心来结束我们对网络核心的介绍
well let's wrap up our introduction to
the network core by coming back to a phrase that i've mentioned a couple
我在说互联网时曾多次提到的一句话
of times when i've said the internet as a network of networks what does
作为一个网络网络，这到底意味着什么？
that really mean and how is that  actually reflected in the structure of  the internet
实际上反映在互联网的结构上
是的，就像我被困在互联网上一样
that really mean and how is that  actually reflected in the structure of  the internet
yikes it's like i'm stuck inside the
是的，就像我被困在互联网上一样
internet here well what we've seen so far is that the users at the
到目前为止，我们所看到的是网络边缘的用户
连接到接入网络，无论是在家
internet here well what we've seen so far is that the users at the
edge of the network are attached to access networks whether that be home networks
网络移动网络机构网络和某种方式我们
mobile networks institutional networks and some way we need a way to connect these
需要一种方法将这数以百万计的接入网络连接在一起
彼此获得用户之间的端到端路径如何可能
millions of access networks together to each other to get end to end paths
我们做得很好，我们可以连接每个线
between users how might we do that well we could connect that is wire
访问每个其他访问 isp 的 isp 但这需要 n 阶平方
each access isp to every other access isp but this would require order n
连接数，当 n 为数百万时，这种方法不会扩展
squared connections and when n is many millions this approach isn't going to scale
考虑到数以百万计的接入互联网服务提供商，我们可能会创建一个全球中转互联网服务提供商
so given the millions of access isps we might create one global transit isp
然后，边缘的每个互联网服务提供商将连接到全球传输网络
each isp at the edge would then connect
to the global transit network
一个主干网络，如果你愿意，一个访问 isp 将到达另一个访问
a backbone network if you will and one
access isp would reach another access
isp 通过这个骨干网络并在
isp
through this backbone network and in the
早期的计算机网络确实如此
early days of computer networking this
was indeed how
边缘网络相互连接
edge networks were interconnected to
each other
但当然，如果一个全球互联网服务提供商是一项可行的业务
but of course if one global isp is a
viable business
他们将成为骨干网服务和这些全球
they'll be competitors for backbone
network service and these global
骨干网将需要相互互连
backbone networks will need to be
interconnected to each other
我们说当一个网络直接与另一个网络对等时
we say that a network peers with another
network when they're directly
互连多个网络的位置
interconnected
the locations at which multiple networks
可以互相对等有时称为互联网交换
can peer with each other
are sometimes called internet exchange
点或对等点区域网络可能会形成
points or peering points
regional networks might form
离家更近的互联接入网络
interconnect access network closer to
home
并连接到纽约州的全球骨干网
and also connect to the global backbone
in the state of new york
nisernet 纽约州教育和研究网络
nisernet the new york state education
and research networks
是为大学提供互联网访问的区域网络的一个例子
is an example of a regional network that
provides internet access to universities
大学 博物馆 医疗保健设施和 k-12 学校
colleges museums
healthcare facilities and k-12 schools
然后是 google 或 microsoft amazon akamai 等内容提供商
and then content providers like google
or microsoft amazon akamai
可能想要运行他们自己的全球网络，事实上他们确实这样做了
might want to run their own global
networks which in fact they do
使他们的服务和内容贴近最终用户
to bring their services and content
close to the end users
我们在这里看到的这张图片非常接近今天的结构
and this picture that we see here is
pretty close to the structure of today's
互联网我们说互联网是一个网络 ，现在您已经了解它的真正含义
internet
we said that the internet is a network
互联网我们说互联网是一个网络 ，现在您已经了解它的真正含义
of networks and now you've got a sense
of what that really means
在互联网的中心，我们拥有相对较少的
at the center of the internet we have a
relatively small number of
连接良好的大型网络，这些有时是
well-connected
large networks these are sometimes
称为 1 级商业 isps，例如 3 级冲刺
called tier 1
commercial isps such as level 3 sprint
在 t ntt 有国内和国际覆盖
at t ntt that have national and
international coverage
靠近边缘的是区域网络，所有这些网络
moving closer to the edge there are the
regional networks all of which
互连，也就是说彼此对等
interconnect that's to say peer with
each other
并与一级供应商并在网络的最边缘
and with tier one providers and at the
very edge of the network then
是接入网络本身，当然还有内容
are the access networks themselves and
then of course there are the content
供应商网络，如 google 和 facebook
provider networks like google and
facebook
将其数据中心和服务连接到
the private networks that connect their
data centers and services to the
互联网，有时绕过第一层和
internet
and sometimes bypassing tier one and
区域互联网服务提供商，只是为了让您了解什么是
regional isps
and just to give you an idea of what a
1 级互联网服务供应商实际上看起来像是最近的 sprint 我们的地图
tier 1 isp actually looks like
here's a recent map of sprint's u.s
网络你可以看到各种国际
network
you can see the various international
此处显示的每个冲刺节点的边缘连接
connections around the edge
each of these sprint nodes shown here is
实际上是一组路由器，它们一起形成了一个所谓的点
actually a collection of routers
that together form a so-called point of
在场或流行音乐这里是流行音乐的爆发，你可以
presence or a pop
here's a blow up of a pop where you can
查看一组将流行路由器连接到客户网络的链接
see a set of links that connect
pop routers down to customer networks
另一组连接到其他冲刺的链接
another set of links that connect to
other sprint
弹出，最后是一组连接到对等网络的路由器，例如
pops and finally a set of routers that
connect to peering networks for example
其他一级网络以及我们对网络的概述
other tier one networks well that
concludes our overview of the network
核心，我们在这里介绍了许多非常重要的概念
core and we've introduced a number of
really important concepts here
我们讲了我们讲的数据包转发过程
we talked about the packet forwarding
process we talked about
存储和转发网络我们谈到了排队延迟
store and forward networks we talked
about queuing delays
丢包的可能性，我们区分
the possibility for packet loss and we
distinguished between
数据包转发和数据包路由我们还讨论了一个替代方案
packet forwarding and packet routing
we also talked about an alternative to
称为电路交换网络的分组交换网络
packet switch networks known as circuit
switch networks
我们讨论了各自的优缺点，最后我们讨论了
and we talked about the pros and cons of
each and we finished up by talking about
那么我们所说的互联网是一个网络的概念是什么意思
well what we mean by that
concept of the internet being a network
在接下来的网络中，我们将采取
of networks
coming up next we're going to take a  look at network performance
查看网络性能 你